<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin
      id="com.esprito.spring"
      url="https://nexus.veeroute.com/repository/esprito-spring-tools/files/esprito-spring-tools-plugin-2023.1.356-232.zip"
      version="2023.1.356-232">
    <idea-version since-build="232.9921.47" until-build="232.*"/>
    <name>Esprito Spring Tools</name>
    <vendor email="support@esprito.com" url="https://esprito.com">Esprito Tech</vendor>
    
<description><![CDATA[
<p>Esprito Spring Tools is an IntelliJ IDEA (Community Edition) plugin designed to enhance your experience with the Spring Framework.</p>
<p>Key Features Include:</p>
<ul>
     <li><strong>Autocompletion:</strong> Autocomplete bean names and navigate through annotations, linking to relevant classes and files.</li>
    <li><strong>Simplified Configuration:</strong> Make working with .properties and .yaml files more efficient through our advanced autocomplete and navigation features.</li>
    <li><strong>Easy Navigation:</strong> Quickly find your way through your project's Spring architecture, improving code understanding.</li>
    <li><strong>Smart Inspections:</strong> Spot and fix common Spring issues early with our targeted checks and fixes.</li>
    <li><strong>JPQL Support:</strong> Maximize your efficiency in JPQL with syntax highlighting and detailed navigation options.</li>
    <li><strong>Kotlin Support:</strong> We support Kotlin, enhancing your Spring projects with seamless integration.</li>
    <li><strong>Code Folding:</strong> Automatically show expected variable values from properties files, simplifying code readability and focus.</li>
    <li><strong>Spring Events Navigation:</strong> Easily move between event publishers and listeners, making your event handling straightforward.</li>
</ul>
<p>Esprito Spring Tools is designed to significantly increase your productivity and accelerate the development of Spring Boot applications.</p>
<p>This plugin is available for free for non-commercial use. For more details, see <a href="https://github.com/esprito-plugin/plugin">homepage</a>.</p>
]]></description>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
